Back together?
Ted.
Deep down,
I have always loved you.
And you still
love me, right?
Back when you
betrayed me,
you never said anything about love.
When you humiliated me
with another man,
you never said a thing about love.
And now?
You wanna talk
about love?
Ted, that was all just a misunderstanding, okay?
Let's go home and talk.
Just the two of us.
Ted's not going
anywhere with you.
He has better
options now.
Better options?
You're just the owner of some trash team.
Without Ted,
it would still be at the bottom of the league.
You really think you can call yourself
the better option?
What if I'm not just the owner of the team?
Ted, there's something you don't know about me.
I'm actually the sole heir to the Taylor family.
Uh... wait.
The Taylor family?
The richest family
in the world?
The trillionaires
who have more money than some countries?